LUCAS CANTOR

(610) 202-9708 · lucas@cantor.cloud

PROFILE

I am an information systems engineer with twelve years of experience. My work focuses on providing highly available, inter-operable, and secure IT infrastructure as a platform. I strive to minimize human error and toil, and to enable automation, self-service, and elimination of complex or high-risk tasks.

EXPERIENCE

Grand Rounds / Senior Systems Engineer San Francisco, CA · OCT 2019 – PRESENT

At Grand Rounds, I am responsible for the automation, availability, and security of an HR-mastered identity and access management platform, designed to maintain HITRUST CSF compliance for disperse clinical staff throughout the entire country.

Intercom / Senior Systems Engineer San Francisco, CA · SEP 2016 – OCT 2019

At Intercom, I was the technical lead on the team responsible for the foundational IT infrastructure on which all corporate systems were built. I grew and mentored a world-class global IT organization from its inception, and I planned, implemented, and owned industry-leading programs for automated user and systems management.

Lucid / IS&T Administrator Oakland, CA · APR 2015 – JUN 2016

At Lucid, I implemented and managed an enterprise IT infrastructure where there had previously been organic growth for over a decade. I enjoyed the unique opportunity to automate myself out of a job and enable an acquisition.

Apple / Retail Systems Support Engineer Cupertino, CA · SEP 2013 – APR 2015

At Apple, I was responsible for deploying and managing tens of thousands of devices in hundreds of Apple stores around the globe. I maintained high-availability and PCI compliance for employees subject to diverse regulatory requirements and speaking dozens of different languages.

PROJECTS

Identity and Access Management

Program Owner, Lead Engineer

Okta, Duo MFA, and Namely as a master, for HR-driven roll-based access control. Oktabacked Active Directory, enabling Amazon Workspaces cloud developer environments. Okta SSO access to endpoints running macOS, Windows, Linux, and Chrome OS.

Zero-Touch Endpoint ManagementProgram Owner, Lead Engineer

Apple Device Enrollment Program and Jamf Pro for macOS and iOS endpoints. AutoPilot, Intune, and Azure Active Directory for Windows endpoints. Okta integration and federation for seamless SSO during enduser-driven out-of-box setup experience.

Device Trust and BeyondCorp

Program Owner, Lead Engineer

Automated certificate deployment and revocation on all managed endpoints via Jamf Pro and Intune. Context, user, and riskaware attestation and policy enforcement, enabling password-free authentication for most cases, or more factors when needed.

EDUCATION

Georgetown University / Computer Science Washington DC · AUG 2008 – MAY 2012